

CONTACT

- +62 822 3412 9959
- ✓ auliasabri43@gmail.com
- Aceh, Indonesia
- https://auliasabri.netlify.app

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022 AR-RANIRY STATE ISLAMIC UNIVERSITY BANDA ACEH

- Bachelor of Information Technology
- GPA: 3.81 / 4.0

SKILLS

- Frontend developmet using React, NextJS, React Native, and Electron
- Backend devlopment using NodeJS and ExpressJS
- Database MongoDB, MySQL, and PostgreSQL
- Fast learning
- Project management
- Teamwork
- Effective communication
- Critical thinking

LANGUAGES

- Bahasa Indonesia (Fluent)
- English (Intermediate)

Aulia Sabri SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

A Versatile Javascript Programmer. Graduated from UIN Ar-Raniry Banda Aceh Majoring in Information Technology and interest in Mobile and Web System. Have experience in programming field since 2019. Proficiency in used Javascript as a tool to build modern and cross-platform app to increase user experience. Besides that, i have some experience in data science especially deep learning with Python and love to use Figma for design and prototyping.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kerjoo

Frontend Developer

Oct 2022 - PRESENT

- Search Engine Optimization
- Developing new features to enhance the user experience.
- · Maintaning and updating existing website
- · Rewrite and redesign existing website with current technologies
- Collaboration with UI/UX Designer and Backend Developer

Freelance

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

Data Scientist | ML/DL Developer

- Provide ML/DL development.
- Develop a face detection model.
- Mentoring in a voice recognition project

Assessed

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

Frontend Developer

- Built web application.
- Developing features to enhance the user experience.
- Collaboration with UI/UX Designer and Backend Developer

Ar-Raniry State Islamic University

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

Fullstack Developer

- Built a website according to the needs of the institution
- Developing front end website application.
- Developing back-end website application.
- Worked together with System Analyst and UI/UX Designer